{"id": "3", "image_id": "3.jpg", "text": "#MLB #Baseball MLB 2010 World Series San Francisco #Giants DVD New in…", "tokens": ["#", "MLB", "#", "Baseball", "MLB", "2010", "World", "Series", "San", "Francisco", "#", "Giants", "DVD", "New", "in", "…"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "4", "image_id": "4.jpg", "text": "Events Center dealing with Garth Brooks concert ticket issues", "tokens": ["Events", "Center", "dealing", "with", "Garth", "Brooks", "concert", "ticket", "issues"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "5", "image_id": "5.jpg", "text": "This sums up the 2nd Half 😈🏀👭🙌🏾😛 .. #ThunderBasketBallgbb @KierreJames @Milli_Bear96", "tokens": ["This", "sums", "up", "the", "2", "nd", "Half", "😈", "🏀", "👭", "🙌", "🏾", "😛", ".", ".", "#", "ThunderBasketBallgbb", "@", "KierreJames", "@", "Milli_Bear96"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER"]}
{"id": "8", "image_id": "8.jpg", "text": "Yesterday when we went to Jersey for lights and siren parade:)had a lot of fun with my fire family :)", "tokens": ["Yesterday", "when", "we", "went", "to", "Jersey", "for", "lights", "and", "siren", "parade", ":)", "had", "a", "lot", "of", "fun", "with", "my", "fire", "family", ":)"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "12", "image_id": "12.jpg", "text": "Hardwick hall festival 30th April 2016.....though it was supposed to be Spring 😀😀", "tokens": ["Hardwick", "hall", "festival", "30", "th", "April", "2016", ".", ".", ".", ".", ".", "though", "it", "was", "supposed", "to", "be", "Spring", "😀", "😀"], "label": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "13", "image_id": "13.jpg", "text": "NBA: Miami Heat close out Hornets in game seven", "tokens": ["NBA", ":", "Miami", "Heat", "close", "out", "Hornets", "in", "game", "seven"], "label": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "15", "image_id": "15.jpg", "text": "#NFL #Seahawks make rare trade up to draft Jarran Reed", "tokens": ["#", "NFL", "#", "Seahawks", "make", "rare", "trade", "up", "to", "draft", "Jarran", "Reed"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "19", "image_id": "19.jpg", "text": "The 10 Best Yoga Moves for Mega Inflexible People -", "tokens": ["The", "10", "Best", "Yoga", "Moves", "for", "Mega", "Inflexible", "People", "-"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "20", "image_id": "20.jpg", "text": "Candid, blurry photo of me at a Rush concert 😂😄", "tokens": ["Candid", ",", "blurry", "photo", "of", "me", "at", "a", "Rush", "concert", "😂", "😄"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "21", "image_id": "21.jpg", "text": "Soccer couples are the best couples ⚽️❤️", "tokens": ["Soccer", "couples", "are", "the", "best", "couples", "⚽", "️", "❤", "️"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "22", "image_id": "22.jpg", "text": "Buy Your Beyonce 2016 Formation World Tour Concert Tickets Here:", "tokens": ["Buy", "Your", "Beyonce", "2016", "Formation", "World", "Tour", "Concert", "Tickets", "Here", ":"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "23", "image_id": "23.jpg", "text": "Spring Planting Festival on Sunday and Monday", "tokens": ["Spring", "Planting", "Festival", "on", "Sunday", "and", "Monday"], "label": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "24", "image_id": "24.jpg", "text": "Nfl sunday ticket adds live streaming to its base package #news #tech #science", "tokens": ["Nfl", "sunday", "ticket", "adds", "live", "streaming", "to", "its", "base", "package", "#", "news", "#", "tech", "#", "science"], "label": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "31", "image_id": "31.jpg", "text": "Our tired mostly female football team. We will beat you next time photo bomber @JoshNaylor #rebootdevelop #Outfit7", "tokens": ["Our", "tired", "mostly", "female", "football", "team", ".", "We", "will", "beat", "you", "next", "time", "photo", "bomber", "@", "JoshNaylor", "#", "rebootdevelop", "#", "Outfit7"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "33", "image_id": "33.jpg", "text": "Was with you in spirit this am @NumCog from @QueenBeaverPub in TO... next time from your living room! #PremierLeague", "tokens": ["Was", "with", "you", "in", "spirit", "this", "am", "@", "NumCog", "from", "@", "QueenBeaverPub", "in", "TO", ".", ".", ".", "next", "time", "from", "your", "living", "room", "!", "#", "PremierLeague"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "34", "image_id": "34.jpg", "text": "Bring on the summer concerts! ✌🏼️ #SamHunt", "tokens": ["Bring", "on", "the", "summer", "concerts", "!", "✌", "🏼", "️", "#", "SamHunt"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER"]}
{"id": "36", "image_id": "36.jpg", "text": "The final chapter of the fairytale – Leicester gear up for historic Premier League title…", "tokens": ["The", "final", "chapter", "of", "the", "fairytale", "–", "Leicester", "gear", "up", "for", "historic", "Premier", "League", "title", "…"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "38", "image_id": "38.jpg", "text": "#NHLPlayoffs Sharks wait a little longer to find out 2nd-round opponent #Kings", "tokens": ["#", "NHLPlayoffs", "Sharks", "wait", "a", "little", "longer", "to", "find", "out", "2", "nd", "-", "round", "opponent", "#", "Kings"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "40", "image_id": "40.jpg", "text": "The Premier Leagues battle for #ChampionsLeague, Europa qualifying", "tokens": ["The", "Premier", "Leagues", "battle", "for", "#", "ChampionsLeague", ",", "Europa", "qualifying"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-MISC", "O"]}
{"id": "41", "image_id": "41.jpg", "text": "#NHLPlayoffs Winnipeg #Jets Scouting Report", "tokens": ["#", "NHLPlayoffs", "Winnipeg", "#", "Jets", "Scouting", "Report"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "42", "image_id": "42.jpg", "text": "Ready for some soccer action!👦💙⚽", "tokens": ["Ready", "for", "some", "soccer", "action", "!", "👦", "💙", "⚽"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "44", "image_id": "44.jpg", "text": "#ManchesterUnited vs #LeicesterCity | #PremierLeague #LIVE STREAM | Team News and More", "tokens": ["#", "ManchesterUnited", "vs", "#", "LeicesterCity", "|", "#", "PremierLeague", "#", "LIVE", "STREAM", "|", "Team", "News", "and", "More"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "45", "image_id": "45.jpg", "text": "I found my baseball mitt and my first game ball. ((:", "tokens": ["I", "found", "my", "baseball", "mitt", "and", "my", "first", "game", "ball", ".", "(", "(", ":"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "51", "image_id": "51.jpg", "text": "Great to see so many families enjoying Rotary Family Festival @BasRFC", "tokens": ["Great", "to", "see", "so", "many", "families", "enjoying", "Rotary", "Family", "Festival", "@", "BasRFC"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "52", "image_id": "52.jpg", "text": "Atlanta dump Boston out of National Basketball Association...", "tokens": ["Atlanta", "dump", "Boston", "out", "of", "National", "Basketball", "Association", ".", ".", "."], "label": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "54", "image_id": "54.jpg", "text": "Influencer Court Smith on her travels ✈️ When's  your next adventure? 🌍 #influencer", "tokens": ["Influencer", "Court", "Smith", "on", "her", "travels", "✈", "️", "When", "'", "s", "your", "next", "adventure", "?", "🌍", "#", "influencer"], "label": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "56", "image_id": "56.jpg", "text": "Memphis Depay ain't a footballer anymore.. Proper tumblr chick now", "tokens": ["Memphis", "Depay", "ain", "'", "t", "a", "footballer", "anymore", ".", ".", "Proper", "tumblr", "chick", "now"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "58", "image_id": "58.jpg", "text": "Happy #MayDay from all of us to all of you! May Day, or #Beltane - the ‘Fire Festival’", "tokens": ["Happy", "#", "MayDay", "from", "all", "of", "us", "to", "all", "of", "you", "!", "May", "Day", ",", "or", "#", "Beltane", "-", "the", "‘", "Fire", "Festival", "’"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O"]}
{"id": "61", "image_id": "61.jpg", "text": "Game 7, #ThisIsWhyWePlay!! by nba", "tokens": ["Game", "7,", "#", "ThisIsWhyWePlay", "!", "!", "by", "nba"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "63", "image_id": "63.jpg", "text": "Valavuori: Buckets Warriors need from Curry vs. Trailblazers. #NBA #WARRIORSvBLAZERS #NBAPlayoffs", "tokens": ["Valavuori", ":", "Buckets", "Warriors", "need", "from", "Curry", "vs", ".", "Trailblazers", ".", "#", "NBA", "#", "WARRIORSvBLAZERS", "#", "NBAPlayoffs"], "label": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "64", "image_id": "64.jpg", "text": "Love this quote by Jerry Jones. Applies way beyond business/football", "tokens": ["Love", "this", "quote", "by", "Jerry", "Jones", ".", "Applies", "way", "beyond", "business", "/", "football"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "66", "image_id": "66.jpg", "text": "My first SSR event, I guess I really lucky #GranblueFantasy", "tokens": ["My", "first", "SSR", "event", ",", "I", "guess", "I", "really", "lucky", "#", "GranblueFantasy"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC"]}
{"id": "67", "image_id": "67.jpg", "text": "Well done to our U10s today @LancashireFA Charter Standard Mini Festival Had lots of fun and played some great footy", "tokens": ["Well", "done", "to", "our", "U10s", "today", "@", "LancashireFA", "Charter", "Standard", "Mini", "Festival", "Had", "lots", "of", "fun", "and", "played", "some", "great", "footy"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "69", "image_id": "69.jpg", "text": "@NoahResendez @Thadeacon that is the most talentless roster I've ever seen in the NBA, let alone the playoffs", "tokens": ["@", "NoahResendez", "@", "Thadeacon", "that", "is", "the", "most", "talentless", "roster", "I", "'", "ve", "ever", "seen", "in", "the", "NBA", ",", "let", "alone", "the", "playoffs"], "label": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "70", "image_id": "70.jpg", "text": "Rt @NBA The @spurs take 1-0 #SPURSvTHUNDER lead with 124-92 W on Aldridge's 38:", "tokens": ["Rt", "@", "NBA", "The", "@", "spurs", "take", "1", "-", "0", "#", "SPURSvTHUNDER", "lead", "with", "124", "-", "92", "W", "on", "Aldridge", "'", "s", "38", ":"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "71", "image_id": "71.jpg", "text": "#BarunSobti to be the Special Guest of To'ylar Muborak festival in Uzbekistan; as posted by @toylarmuborak on Insta", "tokens": ["#", "BarunSobti", "to", "be", "the", "Special", "Guest", "of", "To", "'", "ylar", "Muborak", "festival", "in", "Uzbekistan", ";", "as", "posted", "by", "@", "toylarmuborak", "on", "Insta"], "label": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "72", "image_id": "72.jpg", "text": "Pre game catch on the field at the @RidersBaseball game! #citydads", "tokens": ["Pre", "game", "catch", "on", "the", "field", "at", "the", "@", "RidersBaseball", "game", "!", "#", "citydads"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "77", "image_id": "77.jpg", "text": "😂 RT @NFLDraftInsider: Ezekial Elliot and his crop tops will fit in perfectly in Dallas", "tokens": ["😂", "RT", "@", "NFLDraftInsider", ":", "Ezekial", "Elliot", "and", "his", "crop", "tops", "will", "fit", "in", "perfectly", "in", "Dallas"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "80", "image_id": "80.jpg", "text": "“@NBA: Dwyane Wade locks in for GAME 7! #NBAPlayoffs", "tokens": ["“", "@", "NBA", ":", "Dwyane", "Wade", "locks", "in", "for", "GAME", "7", "!", "#", "NBAPlayoffs"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "82", "image_id": "82.jpg", "text": "Brazilian soccer legend @Ronaldo is making his presence known at the poker table", "tokens": ["Brazilian", "soccer", "legend", "@", "Ronaldo", "is", "making", "his", "presence", "known", "at", "the", "poker", "table"], "label": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "85", "image_id": "85.jpg", "text": "Outstanding band concert @MonaShoresBand @Jayboyden @CoachBrownMSB @MSMSBands you should all be very proud!", "tokens": ["Outstanding", "band", "concert", "@", "MonaShoresBand", "@", "Jayboyden", "@", "CoachBrownMSB", "@", "MSMSBands", "you", "should", "all", "be", "very", "proud", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "90", "image_id": "90.jpg", "text": "Every time this song comes on I think of football for some reason 😪💔", "tokens": ["Every", "time", "this", "song", "comes", "on", "I", "think", "of", "football", "for", "some", "reason", "😪", "💔"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "92", "image_id": "92.jpg", "text": "View from my seats for game 2 Saturday night... #PensCaps #NHLPlayoffs", "tokens": ["View", "from", "my", "seats", "for", "game", "2", "Saturday", "night", ".", ".", ".", "#", "PensCaps", "#", "NHLPlayoffs"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "93", "image_id": "93.jpg", "text": "Just put the dogs on!!!! #rocksoccer #onefamily #Pabst #whatsnext", "tokens": ["Just", "put", "the", "dogs", "on", "!", "!", "!", "!", "#", "rocksoccer", "#", "onefamily", "#", "Pabst", "#", "whatsnext"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "94", "image_id": "94.jpg", "text": "Are you partying with us tonight at forbidden festival 🎉👀", "tokens": ["Are", "you", "partying", "with", "us", "tonight", "at", "forbidden", "festival", "🎉", "👀"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "95", "image_id": "95.jpg", "text": "Happy birthday Gabby!! Soccer won't be the same without you, i hope today is everything you want! ily🎉💟 @gpiccca", "tokens": ["Happy", "birthday", "Gabby", "!", "!", "Soccer", "won", "'", "t", "be", "the", "same", "without", "you", ",", "i", "hope", "today", "is", "everything", "you", "want", "!", "ily", "🎉", "💟", "@", "gpiccca"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "103", "image_id": "103.jpg", "text": "Jerry Jones Comments on Unsuccesful Trade for Paxton Lynch at 2016 NFL Draft", "tokens": ["Jerry", "Jones", "Comments", "on", "Unsuccesful", "Trade", "for", "Paxton", "Lynch", "at", "2016", "NFL", "Draft"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "105", "image_id": "105.jpg", "text": "My fave tennis star in basketball shoes 🤗", "tokens": ["My", "fave", "tennis", "star", "in", "basketball", "shoes", "🤗"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "107", "image_id": "107.jpg", "text": "this is my favorite picture of @oxcolombo from Parade! Im so proud of her!", "tokens": ["this", "is", "my", "favorite", "picture", "of", "@", "oxcolombo", "from", "Parade", "!", "Im", "so", "proud", "of", "her", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "110", "image_id": "110.jpg", "text": "Spending my Sunday morning watching my favorite baseball player 💙⚾️☘", "tokens": ["Spending", "my", "Sunday", "morning", "watching", "my", "favorite", "baseball", "player", "💙", "⚾", "️", "☘"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "111", "image_id": "111.jpg", "text": "So encouraged by the amazing turn out for Looe Festival of the Sea today despite grim weather! A great day!@thembauk", "tokens": ["So", "encouraged", "by", "the", "amazing", "turn", "out", "for", "Looe", "Festival", "of", "the", "Sea", "today", "despite", "grim", "weather", "!", "A", "great", "day", "!", "@", "thembauk"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "113", "image_id": "113.jpg", "text": "fuck !!!!!!!!! i love baseball", "tokens": ["fuck", "!", "!", "!", "!", "!", "!", "!", "!", "!", "i", "love", "baseball"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "114", "image_id": "114.jpg", "text": "Proud to work for @d_rob4 today!  Such a sweet and polite kid. Best of luck at @CalFootball!", "tokens": ["Proud", "to", "work", "for", "@", "d_rob4", "today", "!", "Such", "a", "sweet", "and", "polite", "kid", ".", "Best", "of", "luck", "at", "@", "CalFootball", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "115", "image_id": "115.jpg", "text": "It's as tight at the bottom of la liga as it is at the top.", "tokens": ["It", "'", "s", "as", "tight", "at", "the", "bottom", "of", "la", "liga", "as", "it", "is", "at", "the", "top", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "116", "image_id": "116.jpg", "text": "What's to Become of NBA Live?", "tokens": ["What", "'", "s", "to", "Become", "of", "NBA", "Live", "?"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "117", "image_id": "117.jpg", "text": "Saturday night fun with the Devils! @ASU_Baseball", "tokens": ["Saturday", "night", "fun", "with", "the", "Devils", "!", "@", "ASU_Baseball"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "118", "image_id": "118.jpg", "text": "Didn't get enough baseball this week!  At the SEC baseball Tourney.", "tokens": ["Didn", "'", "t", "get", "enough", "baseball", "this", "week", "!", "At", "the", "SEC", "baseball", "Tourney", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "119", "image_id": "119.jpg", "text": "Zak got decked in the face with a baseball 10 minutes after this", "tokens": ["Zak", "got", "decked", "in", "the", "face", "with", "a", "baseball", "10", "minutes", "after", "this"], "label": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "122", "image_id": "122.jpg", "text": "The things you need to know to work at a festival...it's not all Fosters y'know!", "tokens": ["The", "things", "you", "need", "to", "know", "to", "work", "at", "a", "festival", ".", ".", ".", "it", "'", "s", "not", "all", "Fosters", "y", "'", "know", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "124", "image_id": "124.jpg", "text": "It's a final. Fairfield defeats @SienaBaseball to capture its first #MAACBaseball Tournament Championship.", "tokens": ["It", "'", "s", "a", "final", ".", "Fairfield", "defeats", "@", "SienaBaseball", "to", "capture", "its", "first", "#", "MAACBaseball", "Tournament", "Championship", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "125", "image_id": "125.jpg", "text": "Join us tonight at @pizzaportCbad for the Civil War North vs. South with @FirestoneWalker and @GreenFlashBeer.", "tokens": ["Join", "us", "tonight", "at", "@", "pizzaportCbad", "for", "the", "Civil", "War", "North", "vs", ".", "South", "with", "@", "FirestoneWalker", "and", "@", "GreenFlashBeer", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "126", "image_id": "126.jpg", "text": "NBA Western Conference Finals: Golden State Warriors shock Oklahoma City Thunder, take…", "tokens": ["NBA", "Western", "Conference", "Finals", ":", "Golden", "State", "Warriors", "shock", "Oklahoma", "City", "Thunder", ",", "take", "…"], "label": ["B-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "128", "image_id": "128.jpg", "text": "#NHLPlayoffs People are wondering — do the Florida #Panthers know what they’re  ...", "tokens": ["#", "NHLPlayoffs", "People", "are", "wondering", "—", "do", "the", "Florida", "#", "Panthers", "know", "what", "they", "’", "re", ".", ".", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "130", "image_id": "130.jpg", "text": "Ayr United - the football club in trouble for doing a kit-launch... without a kit", "tokens": ["Ayr", "United", "-", "the", "football", "club", "in", "trouble", "for", "doing", "a", "kit", "-", "launch", ".", ".", ".", "without", "a", "kit"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "132", "image_id": "132.jpg", "text": "#NBAPlayoffs Report: #Rockets still eyeing Spurs' James Borrego for vacant ...", "tokens": ["#", "NBAPlayoffs", "Report", ":", "#", "Rockets", "still", "eyeing", "Spurs", "'", "James", "Borrego", "for", "vacant", ".", ".", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "133", "image_id": "133.jpg", "text": "John does a soccer pub", "tokens": ["John", "does", "a", "soccer", "pub"], "label": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "137", "image_id": "137.jpg", "text": "Ready for the concert 😊👔🎶", "tokens": ["Ready", "for", "the", "concert", "😊", "👔", "🎶"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "139", "image_id": "139.jpg", "text": "#MVCBaseball Championship: Here are the lineups for the game! First pitch just thrown! #HereWeGo", "tokens": ["#", "MVCBaseball", "Championship", ":", "Here", "are", "the", "lineups", "for", "the", "game", "!", "First", "pitch", "just", "thrown", "!", "#", "HereWeGo"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "140", "image_id": "140.jpg", "text": "everyone got nice quality, up close, artsy pictures from the tyler concert and all i got was this 1 of jasper", "tokens": ["everyone", "got", "nice", "quality", ",", "up", "close", ",", "artsy", "pictures", "from", "the", "tyler", "concert", "and", "all", "i", "got", "was", "this", "1", "of", "jasper"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "141", "image_id": "141.jpg", "text": "Uefa Champions League Final: Real Madrid Vs Atletico Madrid: 7:45pm (You Cant Afford To", "tokens": ["Uefa", "Champions", "League", "Final", ":", "Real", "Madrid", "Vs", "Atletico", "Madrid", ":", "7", ":", "45", "pm", "(", "You", "Cant", "Afford", "To"], "label": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "142", "image_id": "142.jpg", "text": "Ole Miss self-imposes double-digit decrease in football scholarships – ESPN", "tokens": ["Ole", "Miss", "self", "-", "imposes", "double", "-", "digit", "decrease", "in", "football", "scholarships", "–", "ESPN"], "label": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "143", "image_id": "143.jpg", "text": "James: \"In football you never know what can happen. But I prefer to stay at Real Madrid.\"", "tokens": ["James", ":", "\"", "In", "football", "you", "never", "know", "what", "can", "happen", ".", "But", "I", "prefer", "to", "stay", "at", "Real", "Madrid", ".", "\""], "label": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "144", "image_id": "144.jpg", "text": "Sweet roomie moved down to start her summer mission yesterday ❤️Love you @CaitlenBarron NOLA is lucky to have you 😘", "tokens": ["Sweet", "roomie", "moved", "down", "to", "start", "her", "summer", "mission", "yesterday", "❤", "️", "Love", "you", "@", "CaitlenBarron", "NOLA", "is", "lucky", "to", "have", "you", "😘"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "145", "image_id": "145.jpg", "text": "Tom Rowe on NHL Radio", "tokens": ["Tom", "Rowe", "on", "NHL", "Radio"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "146", "image_id": "146.jpg", "text": "Back when NBA players didn't have to watch themselves on Twitter", "tokens": ["Back", "when", "NBA", "players", "didn", "'", "t", "have", "to", "watch", "themselves", "on", "Twitter"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "147", "image_id": "147.jpg", "text": "5 takeaways from @VandyBaseball's SEC Tournament trip", "tokens": ["5", "takeaways", "from", "@", "VandyBaseball", "'", "s", "SEC", "Tournament", "trip"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "148", "image_id": "148.jpg", "text": "Policemen in Seattle wearing masks, made by the Red Cross, during the influenza epidemic, …", "tokens": ["Policemen", "in", "Seattle", "wearing", "masks", ",", "made", "by", "the", "Red", "Cross", ",", "during", "the", "influenza", "epidemic", ",", "…"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "149", "image_id": "149.jpg", "text": "my bank account when I have no money but continue to buy concert tickets:", "tokens": ["my", "bank", "account", "when", "I", "have", "no", "money", "but", "continue", "to", "buy", "concert", "tickets", ":"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "150", "image_id": "150.jpg", "text": "Made the mistake of reading some comments on NYT’s woe-is-WNBA piece. Learned that “basketball is a man’s game.”", "tokens": ["Made", "the", "mistake", "of", "reading", "some", "comments", "on", "NYT", "’", "s", "woe", "-", "is", "-", "WNBA", "piece", ".", "Learned", "that", "“", "basketball", "is", "a", "man", "’", "s", "game", ".", "”"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "151", "image_id": "151.jpg", "text": "Irish festival draws crowds to St. Charles' Frontier Park", "tokens": ["Irish", "festival", "draws", "crowds", "to", "St", ".", "Charles", "'", "Frontier", "Park"], "label": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"id": "152", "image_id": "152.jpg", "text": "Packed tent for #letterslive at #hayfestival. If you have yearned to see Cumberbatch in a tent, now's the chance.", "tokens": ["Packed", "tent", "for", "#", "letterslive", "at", "#", "hayfestival", ".", "If", "you", "have", "yearned", "to", "see", "Cumberbatch", "in", "a", "tent", ",", "now", "'", "s", "the", "chance", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "153", "image_id": "153.jpg", "text": "So proud to play a very small role in getting these WWII veterans to the @500Festival Parade.", "tokens": ["So", "proud", "to", "play", "a", "very", "small", "role", "in", "getting", "these", "WWII", "veterans", "to", "the", "@", "500", "Festival", "Parade", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "154", "image_id": "154.jpg", "text": "The premier league is no place for a team named after a ginger man with a fake arm and a silly bird #playofffinal", "tokens": ["The", "premier", "league", "is", "no", "place", "for", "a", "team", "named", "after", "a", "ginger", "man", "with", "a", "fake", "arm", "and", "a", "silly", "bird", "#", "playofffinal"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "155", "image_id": "155.jpg", "text": "Great day of baseball for Hammonton ⭐️'s with #WillTheThrill. Officially obtained coach ankles.", "tokens": ["Great", "day", "of", "baseball", "for", "Hammonton", "⭐", "️", "'", "s", "with", "#", "WillTheThrill", ".", "Officially", "obtained", "coach", "ankles", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "156", "image_id": "156.jpg", "text": "I'm in Bents Park, South Shields for the Proper Food and Drink Festival! Lovely day for it! @shieldsgazette", "tokens": ["I", "'", "m", "in", "Bents", "Park", ",", "South", "Shields", "for", "the", "Proper", "Food", "and", "Drink", "Festival", "!", "Lovely", "day", "for", "it", "!", "@", "shieldsgazette"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "157", "image_id": "157.jpg", "text": "Power of Social Media Influencers &gt;&gt;", "tokens": ["Power", "of", "Social", "Media", "Influencers", "&", "gt", ";", "&", "gt", ";"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "158", "image_id": "158.jpg", "text": "NBA Trade 2016: Derrick Rose to the Lakers Next Season?...", "tokens": ["NBA", "Trade", "2016", ":", "Derrick", "Rose", "to", "the", "Lakers", "Next", "Season", "?", ".", ".", "."], "label": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "159", "image_id": "159.jpg", "text": "Baseball team plays Washington Co., Monday at 4 pm at Hart Co. in the first round of the #5thRegionTournament.", "tokens": ["Baseball", "team", "plays", "Washington", "Co", ".", ",", "Monday", "at", "4", "pm", "at", "Hart", "Co", ".", "in", "the", "first", "round", "of", "the", "#", "5", "thRegionTournament", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "160", "image_id": "160.jpg", "text": "This is what girls in #conflict zones get instead of education", "tokens": ["This", "is", "what", "girls", "in", "#", "conflict", "zones", "get", "instead", "of", "education"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "161", "image_id": "161.jpg", "text": "Look at all those excellent words flying around your word cloud #nba30day! #Mindfulness is clearly working!", "tokens": ["Look", "at", "all", "those", "excellent", "words", "flying", "around", "your", "word", "cloud", "#", "nba30day", "!", "#", "Mindfulness", "is", "clearly", "working", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "162", "image_id": "162.jpg", "text": "Klay is taking that next step as a basketball player.... interesting", "tokens": ["Klay", "is", "taking", "that", "next", "step", "as", "a", "basketball", "player", ".", ".", ".", ".", "interesting"], "label": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "163", "image_id": "163.jpg", "text": "Watching some of the best in youth basketball this weekend at the USSSA Tournament. Eight courts! #AAU", "tokens": ["Watching", "some", "of", "the", "best", "in", "youth", "basketball", "this", "weekend", "at", "the", "USSSA", "Tournament", ".", "Eight", "courts", "!", "#", "AAU"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "164", "image_id": "164.jpg", "text": "I had to get up for this game😱😱😱 #NBAPlayoffs #OKCvsGSW", "tokens": ["I", "had", "to", "get", "up", "for", "this", "game", "😱", "😱", "😱", "#", "NBAPlayoffs", "#", "OKCvsGSW"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "165", "image_id": "165.jpg", "text": "Real or Atletico? Our La Liga pundits make their Champions League final predictions:", "tokens": ["Real", "or", "Atletico", "?", "Our", "La", "Liga", "pundits", "make", "their", "Champions", "League", "final", "predictions", ":"], "label": ["B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "166", "image_id": "166.jpg", "text": "Congrats to my alma mater @dbu_baseball on winning the MVC Tournament. Let's keep it going!", "tokens": ["Congrats", "to", "my", "alma", "mater", "@", "dbu_baseball", "on", "winning", "the", "MVC", "Tournament", ".", "Let", "'", "s", "keep", "it", "going", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "167", "image_id": "167.jpg", "text": "He cares about soccer more than me 💗", "tokens": ["He", "cares", "about", "soccer", "more", "than", "me", "💗"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "168", "image_id": "168.jpg", "text": "Belfast maritime festival with the tall ships 2016. Some interesting characters. #tinyplan…", "tokens": ["Belfast", "maritime", "festival", "with", "the", "tall", "ships", "2016", ".", "Some", "interesting", "characters", ".", "#", "tinyplan", "…"], "label": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "169", "image_id": "169.jpg", "text": "NaVorro Bowman is da best MLB in da game dude is a beast #61 On #NFLTop100", "tokens": ["NaVorro", "Bowman", "is", "da", "best", "MLB", "in", "da", "game", "dude", "is", "a", "beast", "#", "61", "On", "#", "NFLTop100"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "170", "image_id": "170.jpg", "text": "Representing the state of Texas. Two years in a row. #Ramsbaseball.", "tokens": ["Representing", "the", "state", "of", "Texas", ".", "Two", "years", "in", "a", "row", ".", "#", "Ramsbaseball", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "171", "image_id": "171.jpg", "text": "Where LeBron James likes to shoot the ball in the NBA playoffs (video) #LeBronJames", "tokens": ["Where", "LeBron", "James", "likes", "to", "shoot", "the", "ball", "in", "the", "NBA", "playoffs", "(", "video", ")", "#", "LeBronJames"], "label": ["O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER"]}
{"id": "172", "image_id": "172.jpg", "text": "He's got this! 💪  #soccermemes #HalaMadridYNadaMas #Cristiano #ChampionsLeague #penaldo", "tokens": ["He", "'", "s", "got", "this", "!", "💪", "#", "soccermemes", "#", "HalaMadridYNadaMas", "#", "Cristiano", "#", "ChampionsLeague", "#", "penaldo"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "173", "image_id": "173.jpg", "text": "DumireNeva completed the quest Basketball Autograph", "tokens": ["DumireNeva", "completed", "the", "quest", "Basketball", "Autograph"], "label": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "174", "image_id": "174.jpg", "text": "#JeremyLin #NBA Proper Meal Plans For Weight Loss", "tokens": ["#", "JeremyLin", "#", "NBA", "Proper", "Meal", "Plans", "For", "Weight", "Loss"], "label": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "175", "image_id": "175.jpg", "text": "Wembley here we are, thanks to @irnbrufootball #PlayOffFinal", "tokens": ["Wembley", "here", "we", "are", ",", "thanks", "to", "@", "irnbrufootball", "#", "PlayOffFinal"], "label": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "176", "image_id": "176.jpg", "text": "Show your team spirit by joining us for a fundraiser to Support PR Football!", "tokens": ["Show", "your", "team", "spirit", "by", "joining", "us", "for", "a", "fundraiser", "to", "Support", "PR", "Football", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "177", "image_id": "177.jpg", "text": "Four Green Bay-area girls soccer teams earned No. 1 seeds for playoffs", "tokens": ["Four", "Green", "Bay", "-", "area", "girls", "soccer", "teams", "earned", "No", ".", "1", "seeds", "for", "playoffs"], "label": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "178", "image_id": "178.jpg", "text": "Martin Wesolowski with JJ Putz from the Diamond Backs Baseball team. Thanks JJ for supporting #STEAM education.", "tokens": ["Martin", "Wesolowski", "with", "JJ", "Putz", "from", "the", "Diamond", "Backs", "Baseball", "team", ".", "Thanks", "JJ", "for", "supporting", "#", "STEAM", "education", "."], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "179", "image_id": "179.jpg", "text": "Happiest man on this planet for the day. #Cristiano #Zidane #uefafinal", "tokens": ["Happiest", "man", "on", "this", "planet", "for", "the", "day", ".", "#", "Cristiano", "#", "Zidane", "#", "uefafinal"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "180", "image_id": "180.jpg", "text": "Zac Brown Band concert! Yahoo!  #ZacBrownBand", "tokens": ["Zac", "Brown", "Band", "concert", "!", "Yahoo", "!", "#", "ZacBrownBand"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER"]}
{"id": "181", "image_id": "181.jpg", "text": "The water bottle giveaway at the Dupage Drones game @LisleBaseball", "tokens": ["The", "water", "bottle", "giveaway", "at", "the", "Dupage", "Drones", "game", "@", "LisleBaseball"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "182", "image_id": "182.jpg", "text": "20 Times @Drake's Facial Expressions Were More Entertaining Than NBA Games Themselves:", "tokens": ["20", "Times", "@", "Drake", "'", "s", "Facial", "Expressions", "Were", "More", "Entertaining", "Than", "NBA", "Games", "Themselves", ":"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "183", "image_id": "183.jpg", "text": "#NHLPlayoffs #Lightning take Game 5 and the series lead", "tokens": ["#", "NHLPlayoffs", "#", "Lightning", "take", "Game", "5", "and", "the", "series", "lead"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "184", "image_id": "184.jpg", "text": "Thirsty Cleveland Indians fans build impressive pyramid of beer #nba", "tokens": ["Thirsty", "Cleveland", "Indians", "fans", "build", "impressive", "pyramid", "of", "beer", "#", "nba"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "185", "image_id": "185.jpg", "text": "DraftKings: Xander Bogaerts, Zack Greinke Among Tom Caron’s Picks #baseball", "tokens": ["DraftKings", ":", "Xander", "Bogaerts", ",", "Zack", "Greinke", "Among", "Tom", "Caron", "’", "s", "Picks", "#", "baseball"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "186", "image_id": "186.jpg", "text": "Mother-daughter annual selfie with @jojo2511 #HayFestival", "tokens": ["Mother", "-", "daughter", "annual", "selfie", "with", "@", "jojo2511", "#", "HayFestival"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-MISC"]}
{"id": "187", "image_id": "187.jpg", "text": "Last night my exchange took me to see the light and music festival, Vivid Sydney. It was amazing!", "tokens": ["Last", "night", "my", "exchange", "took", "me", "to", "see", "the", "light", "and", "music", "festival", ",", "Vivid", "Sydney", ".", "It", "was", "amazing", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "188", "image_id": "188.jpg", "text": "Interview: Premier League coach vows to remain at expelled club", "tokens": ["Interview", ":", "Premier", "League", "coach", "vows", "to", "remain", "at", "expelled", "club"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "189", "image_id": "189.jpg", "text": "I ❤️ listening to @lorepodcast in public. No one knows I'm learning about sadistic torturer queens while sunbathing!", "tokens": ["I", "❤", "️", "listening", "to", "@", "lorepodcast", "in", "public", ".", "No", "one", "knows", "I", "'", "m", "learning", "about", "sadistic", "torturer", "queens", "while", "sunbathing", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "190", "image_id": "190.jpg", "text": "Lightning hits children’s soccer match in Germany, 35 hurt – Washington Post", "tokens": ["Lightning", "hits", "children", "’", "s", "soccer", "match", "in", "Germany", ",", "35", "hurt", "–", "Washington", "Post"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG"]}
{"id": "191", "image_id": "191.jpg", "text": "#Eagles News: #LeVeonBell gave some advice to #KenjonBarner", "tokens": ["#", "Eagles", "News", ":", "#", "LeVeonBell", "gave", "some", "advice", "to", "#", "KenjonBarner"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER"]}
{"id": "192", "image_id": "192.jpg", "text": "Heartwarming photos of NBA players with their four-legged family", "tokens": ["Heartwarming", "photos", "of", "NBA", "players", "with", "their", "four", "-", "legged", "family"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "193", "image_id": "193.jpg", "text": "Gov. Wike pictured playing football at Yobo's Testimonial Match(Photos)", "tokens": ["Gov", ".", "Wike", "pictured", "playing", "football", "at", "Yobo", "'", "s", "Testimonial", "Match", "(", "Photos", ")"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "194", "image_id": "194.jpg", "text": "Win a Trip to the Wanderlust Aspen-Snowmass Festival in Colorado58", "tokens": ["Win", "a", "Trip", "to", "the", "Wanderlust", "Aspen", "-", "Snowmass", "Festival", "in", "Colorado58"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"id": "195", "image_id": "195.jpg", "text": "How sunflowers track the sun: A sunflower anticipates daybreak.", "tokens": ["How", "sunflowers", "track", "the", "sun", ":", "A", "sunflower", "anticipates", "daybreak", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "196", "image_id": "196.jpg", "text": "#MLB Among Gio Gonzalez’s secret weapons is #Nationals closer Jonathan Papelbon", "tokens": ["#", "MLB", "Among", "Gio", "Gonzalez", "’", "s", "secret", "weapons", "is", "#", "Nationals", "closer", "Jonathan", "Papelbon"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "197", "image_id": "197.jpg", "text": "Yestarday was a great night and tonight we are ready to replicate! #EnnesimoFilmFestival 9pm #TeatroAstoria", "tokens": ["Yestarday", "was", "a", "great", "night", "and", "tonight", "we", "are", "ready", "to", "replicate", "!", "#", "EnnesimoFilmFestival", "9", "pm", "#", "TeatroAstoria"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"id": "198", "image_id": "198.jpg", "text": "Game over Suns-Alna 10-11 #baseball #baseballnorge #KSuns", "tokens": ["Game", "over", "Suns", "-", "Alna", "10", "-", "11", "#", "baseball", "#", "baseballnorge", "#", "KSuns"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "199", "image_id": "199.jpg", "text": "Extreme Core Power for Baseball Workout.", "tokens": ["Extreme", "Core", "Power", "for", "Baseball", "Workout", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "200", "image_id": "200.jpg", "text": "#NFL New York #Jets WR Eric Decker’s OTA Absence No Big Deal", "tokens": ["#", "NFL", "New", "York", "#", "Jets", "WR", "Eric", "Decker", "’", "s", "OTA", "Absence", "No", "Big", "Deal"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "201", "image_id": "201.jpg", "text": "My dad when Barcelona won la liga and me when Madrid won the Champions 😂😂😂😂 #HalaMadrid", "tokens": ["My", "dad", "when", "Barcelona", "won", "la", "liga", "and", "me", "when", "Madrid", "won", "the", "Champions", "😂", "😂", "😂", "😂", "#", "HalaMadrid"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "202", "image_id": "202.jpg", "text": "How Cardiff City are Premier League's richest one-season wonders", "tokens": ["How", "Cardiff", "City", "are", "Premier", "League", "'", "s", "richest", "one", "-", "season", "wonders"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "203", "image_id": "203.jpg", "text": "Tonight Football history changes. The world will never be the same again. Hala Madrid", "tokens": ["Tonight", "Football", "history", "changes", ".", "The", "world", "will", "never", "be", "the", "same", "again", ".", "Hala", "Madrid"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "204", "image_id": "204.jpg", "text": "The legend himself had to come to support Kenyan football @SolManOfficial welcome to Kenya #JengaGame", "tokens": ["The", "legend", "himself", "had", "to", "come", "to", "support", "Kenyan", "football", "@", "SolManOfficial", "welcome", "to", "Kenya", "#", "JengaGame"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "205", "image_id": "205.jpg", "text": "The spot where Piazza and Griffey Jr will live for eternity in the @baseballhall. #Mets", "tokens": ["The", "spot", "where", "Piazza", "and", "Griffey", "Jr", "will", "live", "for", "eternity", "in", "the", "@", "baseballhall", ".", "#", "Mets"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "206", "image_id": "206.jpg", "text": "NBA: RT cavs: \"We earned our right to be here today.\" Nothing is given, everything is earned. GM 6 QUOTES: …", "tokens": ["NBA", ":", "RT", "cavs", ":", "\"", "We", "earned", "our", "right", "to", "be", "here", "today", ".", "\"", "Nothing", "is", "given", ",", "everything", "is", "earned", ".", "GM", "6", "QUOTES", ":", "…"], "label": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "207", "image_id": "207.jpg", "text": "What r u doing this wknd #Festival #flying out #beach Whatever it is dont forget ur #shorts", "tokens": ["What", "r", "u", "doing", "this", "wknd", "#", "Festival", "#", "flying", "out", "#", "beach", "Whatever", "it", "is", "dont", "forget", "ur", "#", "shorts"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "208", "image_id": "208.jpg", "text": "Summer Wine artists demo during Paseo Arts Festival, 28 - 30 May. Go to", "tokens": ["Summer", "Wine", "artists", "demo", "during", "Paseo", "Arts", "Festival", ",", "28", "-", "30", "May", ".", "Go", "to"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "209", "image_id": "209.jpg", "text": "Top @UW_Football prospect Foster Sarell from Graham-Kapowsin. #GETOPEN", "tokens": ["Top", "@", "UW_Football", "prospect", "Foster", "Sarell", "from", "Graham", "-", "Kapowsin", ".", "#", "GETOPEN"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "210", "image_id": "210.jpg", "text": "Not bad for public WiFi speed at a festival. @NWFolklife #folklife", "tokens": ["Not", "bad", "for", "public", "WiFi", "speed", "at", "a", "festival", ".", "@", "NWFolklife", "#", "folklife"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "211", "image_id": "211.jpg", "text": "WTF is she doing on the tele during football!!", "tokens": ["WTF", "is", "she", "doing", "on", "the", "tele", "during", "football", "!", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "212", "image_id": "212.jpg", "text": "#NFL #Saints sign veteran receiver Vincent Brown", "tokens": ["#", "NFL", "#", "Saints", "sign", "veteran", "receiver", "Vincent", "Brown"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "213", "image_id": "213.jpg", "text": "#NFL New #Packers tight end has been a big fan of Rodgers", "tokens": ["#", "NFL", "New", "#", "Packers", "tight", "end", "has", "been", "a", "big", "fan", "of", "Rodgers"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER"]}
{"id": "214", "image_id": "214.jpg", "text": "#MLB Texas #Rangers Promote Joey Gallo, Among Many Roster Moves", "tokens": ["#", "MLB", "Texas", "#", "Rangers", "Promote", "Joey", "Gallo", ",", "Among", "Many", "Roster", "Moves"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "215", "image_id": "215.jpg", "text": "Damian Lewis and Iwan Rheon join final Soccer Aid line-up...", "tokens": ["Damian", "Lewis", "and", "Iwan", "Rheon", "join", "final", "Soccer", "Aid", "line", "-", "up", ".", ".", "."], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "216", "image_id": "216.jpg", "text": "Damn OKC. This shirt, tho. 😱😂😱😂 #OKCvsGSW #NBAFinals", "tokens": ["Damn", "OKC", ".", "This", "shirt", ",", "tho", ".", "😱", "😂", "😱", "😂", "#", "OKCvsGSW", "#", "NBAFinals"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "217", "image_id": "217.jpg", "text": "@Tourism_gov_za. Deputy Minister officially opens the Mzansi International Culinary Festival, at Tintswalo Hotel", "tokens": ["@", "Tourism_gov_za", ".", "Deputy", "Minister", "officially", "opens", "the", "Mzansi", "International", "Culinary", "Festival", ",", "at", "Tintswalo", "Hotel"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"id": "218", "image_id": "218.jpg", "text": "Every time I see this photo, I hear my mother, the acclaimed concert pianist, behind me. Sr. Art Dir. David Adler.", "tokens": ["Every", "time", "I", "see", "this", "photo", ",", "I", "hear", "my", "mother", ",", "the", "acclaimed", "concert", "pianist", ",", "behind", "me", ".", "Sr", ".", "Art", "Dir", ".", "David", "Adler", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"]}
{"id": "219", "image_id": "219.jpg", "text": "#NBAPlayoffs #Clippers Neil Olshey's Track Record in Trades and Free Agency", "tokens": ["#", "NBAPlayoffs", "#", "Clippers", "Neil", "Olshey", "'", "s", "Track", "Record", "in", "Trades", "and", "Free", "Agency"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "220", "image_id": "220.jpg", "text": "My beauty and me. Dance team in the Ski to Sea parade!! by amyhatvany", "tokens": ["My", "beauty", "and", "me", ".", "Dance", "team", "in", "the", "Ski", "to", "Sea", "parade", "!", "!", "by", "amyhatvany"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "221", "image_id": "221.jpg", "text": "😕RT @FootballFunnys: Jamie Lannister has made the trip from Westeros to the San Siro. Incredible support!", "tokens": ["😕", "RT", "@", "FootballFunnys", ":", "Jamie", "Lannister", "has", "made", "the", "trip", "from", "Westeros", "to", "the", "San", "Siro", ".", "Incredible", "support", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "222", "image_id": "222.jpg", "text": "NHL Rumors: Goalie Market, Red Wings and Avalanche", "tokens": ["NHL", "Rumors", ":", "Goalie", "Market", ",", "Red", "Wings", "and", "Avalanche"], "label": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG"]}
{"id": "223", "image_id": "223.jpg", "text": ".@HullCity are back in the @PremierLeague!", "tokens": [".", "@", "HullCity", "are", "back", "in", "the", "@", "PremierLeague", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "224", "image_id": "224.jpg", "text": "i didn't understand the symbolism to this.... there's a dmb concert 4 u", "tokens": ["i", "didn", "'", "t", "understand", "the", "symbolism", "to", "this", ".", ".", ".", ".", "there", "'", "s", "a", "dmb", "concert", "4", "u"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "225", "image_id": "225.jpg", "text": "In a sea of green watching Mexico against Paraguay at the Georgia Dome #realfootball", "tokens": ["In", "a", "sea", "of", "green", "watching", "Mexico", "against", "Paraguay", "at", "the", "Georgia", "Dome", "#", "realfootball"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "226", "image_id": "226.jpg", "text": "@JellyAndDay1 I'm at a concert guys 🤗", "tokens": ["@", "JellyAndDay1", "I", "'", "m", "at", "a", "concert", "guys", "🤗"], "label": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "227", "image_id": "227.jpg", "text": "Our awards are hand blown crystal #SupportIndieFilm #filmfestivals", "tokens": ["Our", "awards", "are", "hand", "blown", "crystal", "#", "SupportIndieFilm", "#", "filmfestivals"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "228", "image_id": "228.jpg", "text": "Even if you don't open to our Chinese concert, we will still like you. Can you just want to understand.@troyesivan", "tokens": ["Even", "if", "you", "don", "'", "t", "open", "to", "our", "Chinese", "concert", ",", "we", "will", "still", "like", "you", ".", "Can", "you", "just", "want", "to", "understand", ".", "@", "troyesivan"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER"]}
{"id": "229", "image_id": "229.jpg", "text": "Brilliant concert tonight at the Torch Theatre for Milford Haven Town Bands Summer Concert #proudconductor", "tokens": ["Brilliant", "concert", "tonight", "at", "the", "Torch", "Theatre", "for", "Milford", "Haven", "Town", "Bands", "Summer", "Concert", "#", "proudconductor"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "230", "image_id": "230.jpg", "text": "Beach boys performing at rehearsal for the Memorial Day concert at the Capitol", "tokens": ["Beach", "boys", "performing", "at", "rehearsal", "for", "the", "Memorial", "Day", "concert", "at", "the", "Capitol"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"id": "231", "image_id": "231.jpg", "text": "Just half an hour left to stop by and see us at the Gin Festival!", "tokens": ["Just", "half", "an", "hour", "left", "to", "stop", "by", "and", "see", "us", "at", "the", "Gin", "Festival", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O"]}
{"id": "232", "image_id": "232.jpg", "text": "Fantastic weekend of bubble football. We're ready to go again and the sun is shining 🎉☀️🍺", "tokens": ["Fantastic", "weekend", "of", "bubble", "football", ".", "We", "'", "re", "ready", "to", "go", "again", "and", "the", "sun", "is", "shining", "🎉", "☀", "️", "🍺"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "233", "image_id": "233.jpg", "text": "Mamadou Sakho's future still in the dark over UEFA hearing", "tokens": ["Mamadou", "Sakho", "'", "s", "future", "still", "in", "the", "dark", "over", "UEFA", "hearing"], "label": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "234", "image_id": "234.jpg", "text": "Rootin for Colorado Rapid tonight with two of my favorite guys - they love their soccer.", "tokens": ["Rootin", "for", "Colorado", "Rapid", "tonight", "with", "two", "of", "my", "favorite", "guys", "-", "they", "love", "their", "soccer", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "235", "image_id": "235.jpg", "text": "Great day at Wembley last Saturday. Much more football this summer on 3. #EURO2016 first up England v Russia June 11", "tokens": ["Great", "day", "at", "Wembley", "last", "Saturday", ".", "Much", "more", "football", "this", "summer", "on", "3", ".", "#", "EURO2016", "first", "up", "England", "v", "Russia", "June", "11"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "236", "image_id": "236.jpg", "text": "The premier place for football fans, especially on a day like today. #halamadrid #championsleague", "tokens": ["The", "premier", "place", "for", "football", "fans", ",", "especially", "on", "a", "day", "like", "today", ".", "#", "halamadrid", "#", "championsleague"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC"]}
{"id": "237", "image_id": "237.jpg", "text": "Only Olly will be on stage at #AberdareFestival 3:15pm", "tokens": ["Only", "Olly", "will", "be", "on", "stage", "at", "#", "AberdareFestival", "3", ":", "15", "pm"], "label": ["O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "238", "image_id": "238.jpg", "text": "One benefit of an 8 hour delay due to the  #thunderstorms is this sweet #Lightning shot over the city #houstonflood", "tokens": ["One", "benefit", "of", "an", "8", "hour", "delay", "due", "to", "the", "#", "thunderstorms", "is", "this", "sweet", "#", "Lightning", "shot", "over", "the", "city", "#", "houstonflood"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "239", "image_id": "239.jpg", "text": "Happy birthday to one of the greatest MLB ever @NBowman53", "tokens": ["Happy", "birthday", "to", "one", "of", "the", "greatest", "MLB", "ever", "@", "NBowman53"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-PER"]}
{"id": "240", "image_id": "240.jpg", "text": "#NBAPlayoffs #Rockets Sending Happy Birthday Wishes to Tracy McGrady", "tokens": ["#", "NBAPlayoffs", "#", "Rockets", "Sending", "Happy", "Birthday", "Wishes", "to", "Tracy", "McGrady"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER"]}
{"id": "241", "image_id": "241.jpg", "text": "As a football fan I am saying Atlético totally did deserve it more than any other club", "tokens": ["As", "a", "football", "fan", "I", "am", "saying", "Atlético", "totally", "did", "deserve", "it", "more", "than", "any", "other", "club"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "244", "image_id": "244.jpg", "text": "My boy in his soccer kit!  Love you buddy!", "tokens": ["My", "boy", "in", "his", "soccer", "kit", "!", "Love", "you", "buddy", "!"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "246", "image_id": "246.jpg", "text": "New Story: Holt High School Junior Varsity Baseball beat Grand Ledge High School 5-4", "tokens": ["New", "Story", ":", "Holt", "High", "School", "Junior", "Varsity", "Baseball", "beat", "Grand", "Ledge", "High", "School", "5", "-", "4"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "248", "image_id": "248.jpg", "text": "info on baseball scholarships at", "tokens": ["info", "on", "baseball", "scholarships", "at"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "250", "image_id": "250.jpg", "text": "There's no crying in baseball! — Tom Hanks in A League Of Their Own. Order now at outona…", "tokens": ["There", "'", "s", "no", "crying", "in", "baseball", "!", "—", "Tom", "Hanks", "in", "A", "League", "Of", "Their", "Own", ".", "Order", "now", "at", "outona", "…"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "251", "image_id": "251.jpg", "text": "@Arsenal when he waved to me at the 2014 FA Cup parade:", "tokens": ["@", "Arsenal", "when", "he", "waved", "to", "me", "at", "the", "2014", "FA", "Cup", "parade", ":"], "label": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "253", "image_id": "253.jpg", "text": "Baseball Game - After a long time (app 2 hours) in the Smith's Ballpark Salt Lake City I got absolutely no idea, ho…", "tokens": ["Baseball", "Game", "-", "After", "a", "long", "time", "(", "app", "2", "hours", ")", "in", "the", "Smith", "'", "s", "Ballpark", "Salt", "Lake", "City", "I", "got", "absolutely", "no", "idea", ",", "ho", "…"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "256", "image_id": "256.jpg", "text": "I moved Elli's beanbag into the sun", "tokens": ["I", "moved", "Elli", "'", "s", "beanbag", "into", "the", "sun"], "label": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "258", "image_id": "258.jpg", "text": "We're at Wymondham Windmill Beer Festival on June 4th. Will you be? (Yep, if you ever want a pint in my pub again)", "tokens": ["We", "'", "re", "at", "Wymondham", "Windmill", "Beer", "Festival", "on", "June", "4", "th", ".", "Will", "you", "be", "?", "(", "Yep", ",", "if", "you", "ever", "want", "a", "pint", "in", "my", "pub", "again", ")"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "259", "image_id": "259.jpg", "text": "See videos from Kermit and Fozzie's appearance at Vulture Festival", "tokens": ["See", "videos", "from", "Kermit", "and", "Fozzie", "'", "s", "appearance", "at", "Vulture", "Festival"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "B-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MISC", "I-MISC"]}
{"id": "261", "image_id": "261.jpg", "text": "It's all a conspiracy folks created by the NHL and aliens.", "tokens": ["It", "'", "s", "all", "a", "conspiracy", "folks", "created", "by", "the", "NHL", "and", "aliens", "."], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "263", "image_id": "263.jpg", "text": "Everyone come out and support your favorite guys and watch some quality basketball this summer 🏀😉", "tokens": ["Everyone", "come", "out", "and", "support", "your", "favorite", "guys", "and", "watch", "some", "quality", "basketball", "this", "summer", "🏀", "😉"], "label": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "264", "image_id": "264.jpg", "text": "World Architecture Festival Announces Judges for 2016", "tokens": ["World", "Architecture", "Festival", "Announces", "Judges", "for", "2016"], "label": ["B-MISC", "I-MISC", "I-MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
